A Guide to the Militia Commission Papers, 1777-1858
Library of Virginia
- Series II. Militia Commissions, 1777-1858., Extent: 66.71 cu. ft. (169 boxes). (Box 3-171)
  - Subseries A. Counties, 1777-1858.
    - Braxton County, 1839. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Braxton County, 1840. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Braxton County, 1841. (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Braxton County, 1842. (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Braxton County, 1843. (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Braxton County, 1844. (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Braxton County, 1845. (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Braxton County, 1846. (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Braxton County, 1847. (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Braxton County, 1848. (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Braxton County, 1849. (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Braxton County, 1850. (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Braxton County, 1851. (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Braxton County, 1852. (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Braxton County, 1853. (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Brooke County, 1797. (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Brooke County, 1798. (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Brooke County, 1799. (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Brooke County, 1800. (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Brooke County, 1801. (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Brooke County, 1802. (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Brooke County, 1804. (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Brooke County, 1806. (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Brooke County, 1808. (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Brooke County, 1809. (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Brooke County, 1811. (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Brooke County, 1812. (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Brooke County, 1813. (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Brooke County, 1814. (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Brooke County, 1815. (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Brooke County, 1816. (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Brooke County, 1817. (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Brooke County, 1818. (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Brooke County, 1819. (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Brooke County, 1821. (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Brooke County, 1823. (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Brooke County, 1824. (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Brooke County, 1825. (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - Brooke County, 1826. (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Brooke County, 1827. (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Brooke County, 1828. (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - Brooke County, 1829. (Box 21, Folder 48)
    - Brooke County, 1832. (Box 21, Folder 49)
    - Brooke County, 1834. (Box 21, Folder 50)
    - Brooke County, 1836. (Box 21, Folder 51)
    - Brooke County, 1837. (Box 21, Folder 52)
    - Brooke County, 1839. (Box 21, Folder 53)
    - Brooke County, 1840. (Box 21, Folder 54)
    - Brooke County, 1841. (Box 21, Folder 55)
    - Brooke County, 1842. (Box 21, Folder 56)
    - Brooke County, 1843. (Box 21, Folder 57)
    - Brooke County, 1844. (Box 21, Folder 58)
    - Brooke County, 1845. (Box 21, Folder 59)
    - Brooke County, 1846. (Box 21, Folder 60)
    - Brooke County, 1847. (Box 21, Folder 61)
    - Brooke County, 1848. (Box 21, Folder 62)
    - Brooke County, 1849. (Box 21, Folder 63)
    - Brooke County, 1850. (Box 21, Folder 64)
    - Brooke County, 1852. (Box 21, Folder 65)
    - Brunswick County, 1785. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Brunswick County, 1786. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Brunswick County, 1788. (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Brunswick County, 1789. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Brunswick County, 1790. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Brunswick County, 1791. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Brunswick County, 1792. (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Brunswick County, 1793. (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Brunswick County, 1794. (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Brunswick County, 1795. (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Brunswick County, 1796. (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Brunswick County, 1797. (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Brunswick County, 1798. (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Brunswick County, 1799. (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Brunswick County, 1800. (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Brunswick County, 1801. (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Brunswick County, 1802. (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Brunswick County, 1803. (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Brunswick County, 1804. (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Brunswick County, 1805. (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Brunswick County, 1806. (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Brunswick County, 1807. (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Brunswick County, 1808. (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Brunswick County, 1809. (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Brunswick County, 1810. (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Brunswick County, 1811. (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Brunswick County, 1812. (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Brunswick County, 1813. (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Brunswick County, 1814. (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Brunswick County, 1815. (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Brunswick County, 1816. (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Brunswick County, 1817. (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Brunswick County, 1818. (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Brunswick County, 1819. (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Brunswick County, 1820. (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Brunswick County, 1821. (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Brunswick County, 1822. (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Brunswick County, 1823. (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Brunswick County, 1824. (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Brunswick County, 1825. (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Brunswick County, 1826. (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Brunswick County, 1827. (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Brunswick County, 1828. (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - Brunswick County, 1829. (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - Brunswick County, 1830. (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - Brunswick County, 1831. (Box 22, Folder 46)
    - Brunswick County, 1832. (Box 22, Folder 47)
    - Brunswick County, 1833. (Box 22, Folder 48)
    - Brunswick County, 1834. (Box 22, Folder 49)
    - Brunswick County, 1835. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Brunswick County, 1836. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Brunswick County, 1837. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Brunswick County, 1838. (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Brunswick County, 1839. (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Brunswick County, 1840. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Brunswick County, 1841. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Brunswick County, 1842. (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Brunswick County, 1843. (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Brunswick County, 1844. (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Brunswick County, 1845. (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Brunswick County, 1846. (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Brunswick County, 1847. (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Brunswick County, 1848. (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Brunswick County, 1849. (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Brunswick County, 1850. (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Brunswick County, 1851. (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Brunswick County, 1852. (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Brunswick County, 1853. (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Brunswick County, 1856. (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Brunswick County, undated. (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Buchanan County, 1845. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Buckingham County, 1781. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Buckingham County, 1785. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Buckingham County, 1786. (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Buckingham County, 1787. (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Buckingham County, 1788. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Buckingham County, 1789. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Buckingham County, 1791. (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Buckingham County, 1792. (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Buckingham County, 1794. (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Buckingham County, 1795. (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Buckingham County, 1796. (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Buckingham County, 1797. (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Buckingham County, 1798. (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Buckingham County, 1799. (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Buckingham County, 1800. (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Buckingham County, 1801. (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Buckingham County, 1802. (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Buckingham County, 1803. (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Buckingham County, 1804. (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Buckingham County, 1805. (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Buckingham County, 1806. (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Buckingham County, 1807. (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Buckingham County, 1808. (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Buckingham County, 1809. (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Buckingham County, 1810. (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Buckingham County, 1811. (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Buckingham County, 1812. (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Buckingham County, 1813. (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Buckingham County, 1814. (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Buckingham County, 1815. (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Buckingham County, 1816. (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Buckingham County, 1817. (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Buckingham County, 1818. (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Buckingham County, 1819. (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Buckingham County, 1820. (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Buckingham County, 1821. (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Buckingham County, 1822. (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Buckingham County, 1823. (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Buckingham County, 1824. (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Buckingham County, 1825. (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - Buckingham County, 1826. (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - Buckingham County, 1827. (Box 24, Folder 43)
    - Buckingham County, 1828. (Box 24, Folder 44)
    - Buckingham County, 1829. (Box 24, Folder 45)
    - Buckingham County, 1830. (Box 24, Folder 46)
    - Buckingham County, 1831. (Box 24, Folder 47)
    - Buckingham County, 1832. (Box 24, Folder 48)
    - Buckingham County, 1833. (Box 24, Folder 49)
    - Buckingham County, 1834. (Box 24, Folder 50)
    - Buckingham County, 1835. (Box 24, Folder 51)
    - Buckingham County, 1836. (Box 24, Folder 52)
    - Buckingham County, 1837. (Box 24, Folder 53)
    - Buckingham County, 1838. (Box 24, Folder 54)
    - Buckingham County, 1839. (Box 24, Folder 55)
    - Buckingham County, 1840. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Buckingham County, 1841. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Buckingham County, 1842. (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Buckingham County, 1843. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Buckingham County, 1844. (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Buckingham County, 1845. (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Buckingham County, 1846. (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Buckingham County, 1847. (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Buckingham County, 1848. (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Buckingham County, 1849. (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Buckingham County, 1850. (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Buckingham County, 1851. (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Buckingham County, 1852. (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Buckingham County, 1853. (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Buckingham County, 1856. (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Buckingham County, undated. (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Cabell County, 1809. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Cabell County, 1810. (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Cabell County, 1811. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Cabell County, 1812. (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Cabell County, 1813. (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Cabell County, 1814. (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Cabell County, 1815. (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Cabell County, 1816. (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Cabell County, 1817. (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Cabell County, 1818. (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Cabell County, 1819. (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Cabell County, 1820. (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Cabell County, 1821. (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Cabell County, 1822. (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Cabell County, 1823. (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Cabell County, 1824. (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Cabell County, 1825. (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Cabell County, 1826. (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Cabell County, 1827. (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Cabell County, 1829. (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Cabell County, 1838. (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Cabell County, 1839. (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Cabell County, 1840. (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Cabell County, 1841. (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Cabell County, 1842. (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Cabell County, 1843. (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Cabell County, 1844. (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Cabell County, 1845. (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Cabell County, 1846. (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Cabell County, 1847. (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Cabell County, 1848. (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Cabell County, 1849. (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Cabell County, 1850. (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Cabell County, 1851. (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Cabell County, 1852. (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Cabell County, 1853. (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - Cabell County, 1856. (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Campbell County, 1784. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Campbell County, 1785. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Campbell County, 1787. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Campbell County, 1788. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Campbell County, 1789. (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Campbell County, 1790. (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Campbell County, 1791. (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Campbell County, 1792. (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Campbell County, 1793. (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Campbell County, 1794. (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Campbell County, 1795. (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Campbell County, 1796. (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Campbell County, 1797. (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Campbell County, 1798. (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Campbell County, 1799. (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Campbell County, 1800. (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Campbell County, 1801. (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Campbell County, 1802. (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Campbell County, 1803. (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Campbell County, 1804. (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Campbell County, 1805. (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Campbell County, 1806. (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Campbell County, 1807. (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Campbell County, 1808. (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Campbell County, 1809. (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Campbell County, 1810. (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Campbell County, 1811. (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Campbell County, 1812. (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Campbell County, 1813. (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Campbell County, 1814. (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Campbell County, 1815. (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Campbell County, 1816. (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Campbell County, 1817. (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Campbell County, 1818. (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Campbell County, 1819. (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Campbell County, 1820. (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - Campbell County, 1821. (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - Campbell County, 1822. (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - Campbell County, 1823. (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - Campbell County, 1824. (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - Campbell County, 1825. (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - Campbell County, 1826. (Box 27, Folder 42)
    - Campbell County, 1827. (Box 27, Folder 43)
    - Campbell County, 1828. (Box 27, Folder 44)
    - Campbell County, 1829. (Box 27, Folder 45)
    - Campbell County, 1830. (Box 27, Folder 46)
    - Campbell County, 1831. (Box 27, Folder 47)
    - Campbell County, 1832. (Box 27, Folder 48)
    - Campbell County, 1833. (Box 27, Folder 49)
    - Campbell County, 1834. (Box 27, Folder 50)
    - Campbell County, 1835. (Box 27, Folder 51)
    - Campbell County, 1836. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Campbell County, 1837. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Campbell County, 1838. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Campbell County, 1839. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Campbell County, 1840. (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Campbell County, 1841. (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Campbell County, 1842. (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Campbell County, 1843. (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Campbell County, 1844. (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Campbell County, 1845. (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Campbell County, 1846. (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Campbell County, 1847. (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Campbell County, 1848. (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Campbell County, 1849. (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Campbell County, 1850. (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Campbell County, 1851. (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Campbell County, 1852. (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Campbell County, 1853. (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Campbell County, 1856. (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Campbell County, undated. (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Caroline County, 1783. (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Caroline County, 1784. (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Caroline County, 1785. (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Caroline County, 1786. (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Caroline County, 1787. (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Caroline County, 1788. (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Caroline County, 1789. (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Caroline County, 1792. (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Caroline County, 1793. (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Caroline County, 1794. (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Caroline County, 1795. (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Caroline County, 1796. (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Caroline County, 1797. (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Caroline County, 1798. (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Caroline County, 1799. (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Caroline County, 1800. (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Caroline County, 1801. (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Caroline County, 1802. (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Caroline County, 1803. (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Caroline County, 1804. (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Caroline County, 1805. (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Caroline County, 1806. (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Caroline County, 1807. (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Caroline County, 1808. (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Caroline County, 1809. (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Caroline County, 1811. (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Caroline County, 1812. (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Caroline County, 1813. (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Caroline County, 1814. (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Caroline County, 1815. (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Caroline County, 1816. (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Caroline County, 1817. (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Caroline County, 1818. (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Caroline County, 1819. (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - Caroline County, 1820. (Box 29, Folder 35)
    - Caroline County, 1821. (Box 29, Folder 36)
    - Caroline County, 1822. (Box 29, Folder 37)
    - Caroline County, 1823. (Box 29, Folder 38)
    - Caroline County, 1824. (Box 29, Folder 39)
    - Caroline County, 1825. (Box 29, Folder 40)
    - Caroline County, 1826. (Box 29, Folder 41)
    - Caroline County, 1827. (Box 29, Folder 42)
    - Caroline County, 1828. (Box 29, Folder 43)
    - Caroline County, 1829. (Box 29, Folder 44)
    - Caroline County, 1830. (Box 29, Folder 45)
    - Caroline County, 1831. (Box 29, Folder 46)
    - Caroline County, 1832. (Box 29, Folder 47)
    - Caroline County, 1833. (Box 29, Folder 48)
    - Caroline County, 1834. (Box 29, Folder 49)
    - Caroline County, 1835. (Box 29, Folder 50)
    - Caroline County, 1836. (Box 29, Folder 51)
    - Caroline County, 1837. (Box 29, Folder 52)
    - Caroline County, 1838. (Box 29, Folder 53)
    - Caroline County, 1839. (Box 29, Folder 54)
    - Caroline County, 1840. (Box 29, Folder 55)
    - Caroline County, 1841. (Box 29, Folder 56)
    - Caroline County, 1842. (Box 29, Folder 57)
    - Caroline County, 1843. (Box 29, Folder 58)
    - Caroline County, 1844. (Box 29, Folder 59)
    - Caroline County, 1845. (Box 29, Folder 60)
    - Caroline County, 1846. (Box 29, Folder 61)
    - Caroline County, 1847. (Box 29, Folder 62)
    - Caroline County, 1848. (Box 29, Folder 63)
    - Caroline County, 1849. (Box 29, Folder 64)
    - Caroline County, 1850. (Box 29, Folder 65)
    - Caroline County, 1851. (Box 29, Folder 66)
    - Caroline County, undated. (Box 29, Folder 67)
    - Carroll County, 1839. (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Carroll County, 1842. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Carroll County, 1845. (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Carroll County, 1851. (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Carroll County, 1853. (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Charles City County, 1782. (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Charles City County, 1784. (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Charles City County, 1785. (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Charles City County, 1786. (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Charles City County, 1787. (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Charles City County, 1788. (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Charles City County, 1789. (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Charles City County, 1790. (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Charles City County, 1791. (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Charles City County, 1792. (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Charles City County, 1793. (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Charles City County, 1794. (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Charles City County, 1795. (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Charles City County, 1796. (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Charles City County, 1798. (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Charles City County, 1800. (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Charles City County, 1801. (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Charles City County, 1803. (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Charles City County, 1804. (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Charles City County, 1805. (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Charles City County, 1806. (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Charles City County, 1807. (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Charles City County, 1808. (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Charles City County, 1809. (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Charles City County, 1810. (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Charles City County, 1811. (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Charles City County, 1812. (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Charles City County, 1813. (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Charles City County, 1816. (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Charles City County, 1818. (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Charles City County, 1819. (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Charles City County, 1820. (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - Charles City County, 1821. (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - Charles City County, 1822. (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - Charles City County, 1823. (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - Charles City County, 1824. (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - Charles City County, 1825. (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - Charles City County, 1827. (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - Charles City County, 1828. (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - Charles City County, 1830. (Box 31, Folder 40)
    - Charles City County, 1831. (Box 31, Folder 41)
    - Charles City County, 1832. (Box 31, Folder 42)
    - Charles City County, 1841. (Box 31, Folder 43)
    - Charles City County, 1845. (Box 31, Folder 44)
    - Charles City County, 1846. (Box 31, Folder 45)
    - Charles City County, 1851. (Box 31, Folder 46)
    - Charles City County, 1852. (Box 31, Folder 47)
    - Charles City County, 1854. (Box 31, Folder 48)
    - Charles City County, undated. (Box 31, Folder 49)
    - Charlotte County, 1784. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Charlotte County, 1785. (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Charlotte County, 1786. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Charlotte County, 1787. (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Charlotte County, 1788. (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Charlotte County, 1789. (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Charlotte County, 1791. (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Charlotte County, 1792. (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Charlotte County, 1793. (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Charlotte County, 1794. (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Charlotte County, 1795. (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Charlotte County, 1796. (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Charlotte County, 1797. (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Charlotte County, 1798. (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Charlotte County, 1799. (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Charlotte County, 1800. (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Charlotte County, 1801. (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Charlotte County, 1802. (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Charlotte County, 1803. (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Charlotte County, 1804. (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Charlotte County, 1805. (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Charlotte County, 1806. (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Charlotte County, 1807. (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Charlotte County, 1809. (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Charlotte County, 1810. (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Charlotte County, 1811. (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Charlotte County, 1812. (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Charlotte County, 1813. (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Charlotte County, 1814. (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Charlotte County, 1815. (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Charlotte County, 1816. (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Charlotte County, 1817. (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Charlotte County, 1818. (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Charlotte County, 1819. (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Charlotte County, 1820. (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Charlotte County, 1821. (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - Charlotte County, 1822. (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - Charlotte County, 1823. (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - Charlotte County, 1824. (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Charlotte County, 1825. (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - Charlotte County, 1826. (Box 32, Folder 41)
    - Charlotte County, 1827. (Box 32, Folder 42)
    - Charlotte County, 1828. (Box 32, Folder 43)
    - Charlotte County, 1829. (Box 32, Folder 44)
    - Charlotte County, 1830. (Box 32, Folder 45)
    - Charlotte County, 1831. (Box 32, Folder 46)
    - Charlotte County, 1832. (Box 32, Folder 47)
    - Charlotte County, 1833. (Box 32, Folder 48)
    - Charlotte County, 1834. (Box 32, Folder 49)
    - Charlotte County, 1835. (Box 32, Folder 50)
    - Charlotte County, 1836. (Box 32, Folder 51)
    - Charlotte County, 1837. (Box 32, Folder 52)